http://www.mrsfields.com/privacy/

Mrs. Fields Privacy Policy
Skip to Content
Did you hear about us on Radio or TV?
Enter your radio, TV, or other promotional code for special savings!
Go
Ente Code
Your entry is not recognized.
Did you hear about us on the Radio or TV?
Own a Franchise
Need Help?
Custom Gifts
Buy in Bulk & Save!
Gifts on Sale
Delivering Cookies Safely To Your Door (Nationwide)
Effective: 1/1/2020
Famous Brands International (“Mrs. Fields,” “TCBY,” “We,” “Our,” or “Us”) takes your privacy very seriously. Please carefully read this Privacy Policy and familiarize yourself with our privacy practices regarding your personal information and how we will use it. This Privacy Policy applies to Our site, including mobile sites or apps (collectively, the “Sites”). By visiting the Sites, you accept this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, do not use the Sites.
What information we collect
You may browse the Sites without providing any personally identifiable information. In order to access certain services, you may be asked and we may collect your personally identifiable information at various points throughout the Sites. You may be asked to provide:
Identifiers such as your name;
Contact information such as your email address, mailing address, and phone number;
Financial information such as your credit card number;
Internet and other electronic network activity information such as your IP address, your browsing history on the Sites, the length of time spent on certain pages, the website Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) from the website you were visiting before coming to this Site, which URL you next visit, device type, what browser you are using, Internet service provider, date/time of visit information, and operating system.
Uses of Personal Information
Your information may be used in several ways:
Identifiers and contact information are used:
To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions;
To alert you to new projects, Sites features, special events and services;
To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service;
To enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
To protect our rights or property or our safety, our members, or others;
To comply with any court order, legal process, or respond to any governmental or regulatory request;
To otherwise market products and services that may be of interest to you;
Financial Information is used:
To allow you to make a purchase on the Sites;
Internet and other electronic network activity information is used:
To monitor and evaluate our Sites and identify where we should make changes or expand services;
To
develop new features and services that meet subscriber needs.
Sharing of Personal Information
We may use third-party service providers or other third-party organizations to provide services on our behalf.
Specifically, we will share your personal information with the following categories of third parties:
Our affiliate companies, for purposes of fulfilling an order or other request, or jointly marketing products/services;
Non-affiliated third parties who help us to provide the services that you request. For example, we do not collect or process your financial information for purposes of processing payments; instead, we pass that financial information along to a third party payment processor. We require third parties who are providing services on our behalf to limit their use of your information to the limited purpose for which it was shared, and to employ reasonable security to protect your information;
Non-affiliated third parties who provide products/services that may be of interest to you. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Third party analytics companies that help us to monitor traffic on the Sites, learn how users are navigating our Sites, and help troubleshoot or improve the services we provide;
Law enforcement or legal authorities, in response to lawfully served process or subpoena. Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personal information. We will disclose personal information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, warrant, or other legal process to the extent necessary to meet legal, national security, public interest, or law enforcement obligations. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our Services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful;
Successor company or companies in the event that we cease operations for any reason. In the event that we enter into an agreement to be purchased by another company or to merge with another company, we may share personal information with that company. We will require that such purchasers continue to comply with the provisions as outlined in this Privacy Policy;
Market-research firms, as more fully described below
Research
We may contract with a market-research firm to conduct occasional online surveys. When you're within our sites, you may see a pop-up window offering you the optional opportunity of participating in a survey. If you do not wish to participate, simply click the "No, Thank You" link and you will not see this window again. If you choose to participate, you'll be prompted to answer a series of online questions. You will be prompted to enter your e-mail address for validation purposes but no other personal information will be collected as part of the survey. In some cases, however, you may be offered a free gift for your participation. We will need your name and address, which will be used exclusively to fulfill your gift request.
Cookie Technology
We also employ cookie technology to help subscribers move faster through our site. When you use one of our sites, we pass several cookies to your computer. A cookie is a string of information that's sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. This avoids the potentially time-consuming task of checking our registration database each time a page is requested. The cookie is deleted when a user chooses the log out feature to terminate their session. We also employ cookie technology to store subscribers' User Names and Passwords. Read our cookie disclosure statement and view a cookie-by-cookie breakdown.
Do Not Track
Some web browsers may transmit “Do Not Track” signals to websites visited by the user. Our information collection and disclosure practices will continue to apply as described in this policy, regardless of any “Do Not Track” signals that are sent by certain browsers.
Third Party Web Sites
Our Sites may contain links to other Web sites provided by third parties. Please be aware that we do not control these third-party Web sites or any of the content contained on those Web sites. Once you have left our Sites, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other Web sites. We encourage you to exercise caution and to read the privacy policy for the Web site you visit. The inclusion of hyperlinks to third party Web sites on our Sites in no way constitutes an endorsement by us of such Web sites’ content, actions or policies.
Security
We are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and takes steps to help protect the personal information you provide to us. However, no transmission or electronic storage of information is guaranteed to be secure. We therefore urge you to always use caution when transmitting information over the Internet.
Children
The Sites are not directed toward children under 18 years of age nor do we knowingly collect information from children under 18. If you are under 18, please do not use the Sites or submit any personally identifiable information to us.
California ”Shine the Light”
California’s “Shine The Light” law permits California residents to annually request and obtain information free of charge about what personal information is disclosed to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. We do not disclosure your personal information to third parties for purposes of those third parties marketing their own products or services.
California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, you have the following rights.
Right of Access. You have the right to access your personal information maintained by us. Upon receipt of a verifiable request to access personal information, we will disclose and deliver, free of charge, the personal information requested for the 12-month period preceding your request.
Please note that we are not required to provide personal information to you more than twice in a 12-month period.
Right of Deletion. You have the right to request that we delete any personal information about you which we have collected from you. Upon receipt of a verifiable request for deletion, we will delete your personal information from our records and direct any service providers to delete your personal information from our records, within 45 days.
We will comply with your request to delete personal information unless it is necessary for us to maintain your personal information in order to:
Complete a transaction, provide requested-for goods/services, and/or perform a contract between you and us;
Detect security incidents;
Comply with a legal obligation;
Enable our internal uses that are aligned with your expectations and your relationship with us.
Submission of Requests for Information. We have designated the following methods for California residents to submit requests for information:
By submitting a request via support@mrsfields.com;
By calling 1-800-COOKIES
Verification. After you submit a request, we will promptly take steps to determine whether your request is a verifiable request. We will verify that you are who you say you are by having you provide unique information relating to a recent transaction or order.
We will disclose and deliver the required information to you free of charge within 45 days of receiving your verifiable request. If necessary, we will extend the time period to provide the required information once by an additional 45 days, and will provide you with notice of the extension within the first 45-day period. The disclosure shall cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of the verifiable request.
As noted below, we do not knowingly collect information from or about children, including children aged 18 and under. We do not sell information of minors under 18 years of age.
Authorized Agent. You have the right to designate an authorized agent to submit an access or deletion request on your behalf. If you use an authorized agent to submit such a request, we will require that you:
Provide the authorized agent written permission
to act on your behalf; and
Verify your own identity with us before we can honor the request.
No Sale of Personal Information. We have not sold personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the last 12 months. We do not intend to sell personal information to third parties.
No Discrimination. We will not discriminate against a California resident because the California resident exercised any of the rights described here.
Changes and Updates
We will annually review and may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes on this page and update the date at the top, so be sure to check back periodically to stay aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Sites after changes have been posted will constitute your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any changes.
International Visitors
We store and process your data in the United States, and we intend our services only to be used in the United States. If you are located in a foreign jurisdiction and do not want to transfer your data to the United States or if it is illegal to transfer or process your data in the United States, please do not use our services.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, or to update any information you have provided us, please send us an email to support@mrsfields.com.
Our Privacy Officer
can be reached at support@mrsfields.com or by physical mail at 1717 South 4800 West, Salt Lake City, Utah 84104.
Mrs. Fields Cookies
The original Mrs. Fields Cookie! Our fresh baked personalized cookie gifts & gourmet cookie gift baskets are guaranteed to impress. Order gourmet cookies online and have them delivered to your friends, family, and colleagues.					See our cookie gifts
Holiday Gift Baskets
Spread holiday cheer to all your friends and family with one of Mrs. Fields’ gourmet Holiday gift baskets and
Christmas cookie tins. Shop our collection of Holiday cookies and gift baskets and discover the perfect gift that will be sure to bring a smile to everyone’s face. Choose from freshly baked brownies and Nibblers™, or our soft and tasty classic chocolate chip cookies – you’ll find the sweetest gift baskets for everyone at Mrs. Fields™. Order online or in-store to have your Holiday gifts delivered!
Gift Occasion
Halloween Treats
Appreciation Gifts
Birthday
Back to School Gifts
Holiday Cookie Gifts
Christmas Gifts
Shop By Product
Coupons & Promo Codes
Connect with us:
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Mrs. Fields Secrets
Sign Up
*Discount codes cannot be combined with another code and are not valid on items already on sale, prior orders, or in-store pickups. Holiday deals and bulk items cannot be combined with a discount code; price is as marked. You’re already getting the sweetest deal!
Mrs. Fields Cookies
The original Mrs. Fields Cookie! Our fresh baked personalized gifts & gift baskets are guaranteed to impress.
See our cookie gifts
1-800-COOKIES
Jobs
Need Help?
Buy in Bulk & Save!
